battlemetrics.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy - BattleMetrics

## Privacy Policy

### 1\. General Statement

We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it. This privacy statement explains our policies and practices regarding online user information. It is through this disclosure that we intend to provide you with a level of comfort and confidence in how we collect, use, and safeguard personal and other information we collect or that you provide through this website, and how you can contact us if you have any questions or concerns. It is our sincere hope that by explaining our data handling practices we will develop a trusting and long-lasting relationship with you. By using the site, you agree to the terms of this privacy statement. See also our Terms and Conditions.

### 2\. Information About Our Organization and Website and General Data Collection Practices

This Privacy Statement applies to [www.BattleMetrics.com](http://www.battlemetrics.com/) (referenced herein as “site” or “website”) which is owned by BattleMetrics, LLC, P.O. Box 980789, Ypsilanti, MI 48198.

**Online Tracking Information**

Because there is not yet a common understanding of how to interpret web browser-based “Do Not Track” (“DNT”) signals other than cookies, BattleMetrics, LLC does not currently respond to “DNT” signals to its US websites.

Most browsers can be configured not to accept cookies; however, this may prevent you from having access to some functions or services on our sites.

See Sections 5 and 7 for more information.

### 3\. Personally Identifiable Information We Collect From You

When you visit this site we will not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you provide it to us voluntarily. For purposes of this Privacy Statement, “personally identifiable information” is information that identifies you as an individual, for example your name, street address, telephone number, e-mail address and credit card number. If you opt not to provide us with personally identifiable information you can still access our website, however you will be unable to create login credentials which are necessary to access certain functionalities on the site. Furthermore, you may not be able to activate or use a service, have a purchase order fulfilled, or receive product information.

**BattleMetrics.com - Saving Content**

Some functionality and services we provide you offer the opportunity to save certain content. The information can only be saved by creating login credentials described in the next paragraph.

**BattleMetrics.com - Creating Login Credentials**

Certain pages of this website may allow you to create login credentials by typing in your user name/ID or email address and password and other information, or by using one of the available social media authentication methods such as logging in through the Steam network. If you choose to create login credentials using your account with one of the available social media authentication tools, you allow us to access your information that is publicly available or that you have made publicly available (e.g., name, user ID, profile picture), and information you “Allow” the website to access. By authenticating through one of the social media options, you allow us to receive your information that is accessible. We encourage you to review the privacy policy and any terms and conditions, for the method you choose to utilize for authentication.

### 4\. How We Use the Personally Identifiable Information We Collect

Personally identifiable information collected on this site may be used to:

  * Fulfill a site user request (e.g., create log in credentials, brochure fulfillment, send marketing or promotional materials including e-mails, price quotes, send alerts, send updates, and/or to save or share content)
  * Fulfill and deliver an order for goods or services
  * Respond to your comments or requests for information
  * Meet a request for or to develop new products or services
  * Make the user experience more customer friendly
  * Contact you if necessary in the course of processing or shipping an order for products or services
  * Generate site analytics that improve our site layout, content, product offerings and services
  * Compile user data that is stored in our database
  * Match personal data collected here with data about you that we collect through other sources
  * Comply with legal requirements
  * Send SMS alerts subject to user requested conditions

### 5\. Other Information We Collect From Site Visitors

This site collects other information from site visitors. This means that we do not track these items on an individual basis that identifies the site visitor, but rather gather and collect this information on an aggregate [or anonymous] basis that includes all site visitors. Non-personally identifiable information may include information such as tracking the site pages that are visited, the amount of time spent on our site, clicks, mouse movements, scrolls, page views, events (which shopping tools you interacted with), and zip code. This includes aggregate data provided by a third-party that surveys site visitors on our behalf.

Information that we collect from RCON users is for the sole use of the RCON user and those who the RCON user authorizes to view such information. However, we will use some of the information we obtain over the RCON connection to create more accurate player and server data for the public. In no event will we disclose information obtained over the RCON connection to unauthorized users unless that information is already publicly available. For example, player names are always public, whereas IPs are not. In that situation we would only display the player name to the public and not the IP.

We may use session and persistent “cookies,” session logs, spot light ads/web beacons/GIF/pixel tags, banner ads or links, third-party networks that serve user-requested emails (e.g., a third party email service provider for Tell-a-Friend user-customized emails), and third-party click tracking analytics tools (such as Adobe, DoubleClick, Efficient Frontier, Keynote, Google Analytics and ClickTale; these companies may also use such tools) to collect aggregate or other non-personally identifiable information about site visitors. An explanation on collection methods and how they work is included in Section 7 - Methods to Collect Information, below.

We also use your data for advertising purposes.

We use third-party advertising companies who serve ads to help keep content free. For these partners, we put additional restrictions on how your data can be used to prevent it from misuse. For instance, we do not allow these partners to take your information for profiling and personalizing ads on other sites.

Please review the following for a full list of partners and purposes: -[PubGalaxy (Titan Gate AD)] (<https://www.pubgalaxy.com/privacy-policy.html>)

### 6\. How We Use the Aggregate or Non-Personally Identifiable Information We Collect

Non-Personally identifiable information collected on this site may be used to:

  * Compile aggregate and statistical data to help in website design and to identify popular features
  * Measure site activity to allow us to update our site to better meet user wants and needs
  * Make the user experience more customer friendly

This site utilizes non-personally identifiable information for the purpose of performing analytics on the users' experience while visiting this site. This analysis:

  * Is performed on an aggregate level and does not identify you or your information personally
  * May involve the use of a third-party vendor acting on behalf of this site
  * Is performed in order to improve our website and the user experience

### 7\. Methods to Collect Information and Interest-Based/Online Behavioral Advertising

A “cookie” is a small text file that helps us in many ways to make your visit to our website more enjoyable and meaningful to you. For example, cookies avoid you having to log in every time you come back to one of our websites. They also allow us to tailor a website or advertisement to better match your interests and preferences. There are a couple different types of cookies.

A “session” cookie is stored only in your computer's working memory (RAM) and only lasts for your browsing session. When you close all your browser's windows, or when you shut down your computer, the session cookie disappears forever.

A “persistent” cookie is stored on your computer's hard drive until a specified date, which could be tomorrow, next week, or 10 years from now. Persistent cookies stay on your computer until either a) they expire, b) they are overwritten with newer cookies, or c) you manually remove them. Most browsers can be configured not to accept cookies, however, this may prevent you from having access to some site functions or features.

This site may use a third party to activate and/or deliver a service, or deliver site functionality such as fulfilling your request to purchase a product or service, including items from our online store. In performing this function the third party may place a persistent cookie on your computer or have to gather personal information from you in order to activate and deliver the service, or facilitate the processing of your purchase.

This site may use a third-party click tracking analytics tool (such as Adobe, DoubleClick, Efficient Frontier, Keynote, Google Analytics and ClickTale) to capture clickthrough statistics.

This site may use spotlight ads/web beacons/GIF/pixel tags which are site instrumentation tools that help us to determine, for instance, whether a page has been viewed or not and, if so, how many times. Emails or electronic newsletters we send may use tools (e.g., pixel tags or web beacons) to gather email metrics and information to improve the reader’s experience such as how many of the emails are opened, if they were printed or forwarded, the type of device (e.g., mobile or PC) from which they were opened, and the city, state, and county associated with the applicable IP address. In general, any electronic image viewed as part of a webpage, including an ad banner, can act as a web beacon.

This website may generate a “session log” when you visit our site. We use session logs to help us determine how people travel through our site. In this way, we can structure our pages so that the information most frequently visited is easier to find. By tracking page visits, we can also determine if the information we're providing is being used. The only data gathered is the Internet Protocol (IP) address from which you came (which contains no personal information), the website that referred you, the pages you visited and the date and time of those visits.

Users may be provided the opportunity to integrate with third-party social media sites, and this site may track on an aggregate level the number of items “liked” on this site, or items on this site that you choose to share with a third-party social media site.

Users may be directed to this site via banner ads, site links or QR Codes. Ads, site links or QR Codes may use tools such as cookies or web beacons to deliver metrics on the effectiveness of the ads or links. They do not collect personally identifiable information from the user.

This website also utilizes Google Analytics and its associated cookies. If you wish to opt-out of the tracking associated with Google Analytics, you can download [this](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) addon. Additionally, you may opt-out by adjusting your Ads Settings, Ad Settings for mobile apps, or any other available means (such as the NAI consumer opt-out).

### 8\. Sharing Your Information

This site does not share, sell, or rent personally identifiable information with independent companies for their own use without providing you a choice.

Personally identifiable information that you provide to us in the course of using our site features or requesting a product or service through this website may be gathered and stored in one or more of our corporate databases. For site visitors in the U.S. personally identifiable information may be used for purposes of contacting you for things like promotional offers, marketing programs, or other communications from this website.

Personally identifiable information that you provide to this website, except for mobile numbers provided when requesting text messages and mobile alerts, will not be shared with any entity not owned by BattleMetrics, LLC. Any personally identifiable information shared with third parties will only be shared to the extent necessary to fulfill a user request or user-requested service.

Vendors, contractors or partners of this site who have access to your personally identifiable information in connection with providing services for this site are required to keep the information confidential and are not permitted to use this information for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for this site.

This site may share personally identifiable information with subcontractors. Subcontractors are restricted from using this data in any other way other than to provide these services to BattleMetrics, LLC and they may not share or resell this data.

This site will disclose your personally identifiable information and/or your non-personally identifiable information without notice only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on BattleMetrics, LLC or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of BattleMetrics, LLC and this site; or, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of BattleMetrics, LLC, its web sites, or the public. The rights or property of BattleMetrics, LLC will be implicated in any dispute between you and BattleMetrics, LLC, including but not limited to: disputes over issues of contract, tort, and/or any other legal issue that may arise.

### 9\. Access To and Control Over the Use of Your Personally Identifiable Information

To correct or update your personally identifiable information you may contact us at:

By Mail:

    BattleMetrics, LLC
    P.O. Box 980789
    Ypsilanti, MI 48198

OR By Email: [staff@battlemetrics.com](mailto:staff@battlemetrics.com)

You will be asked for name and address so that we may be able to process your changes. We will use reasonable efforts to correct any factual inaccuracies in your information.

The scope of access available for this request is for information stored in the database that holds the data for this site. Any personally identifiable information that has been collected from you on other websites will not be accessible or changeable through the processing of this request.

### 10\. Security of Your Information

Safeguarding information of visitors to our website is important to us. We use systems, policies and procedures to maintain accuracy of information and to protect information from loss, misuse or alteration.

When you send personally identifiable information, such as name, address and telephone numbers, to this site we use “Secure Socket Layers” or SSL to protect your data. SSL is encryption technology that helps safeguard your personally identifiable information against misuse by unauthorized individuals.

Vendors, contractors or partners of this site who have access to your personally identifiable information in connection with providing services for this site are required to keep the information confidential.

### 11\. Consent to Processing

By visiting this site and by providing your personally identifiable information to us, you understand and consent to the collection, use, processing, transfer, and disclosure of your personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information globally --- including to the United States – in accordance with this Privacy Statement. Therefore, by visiting this site and by providing such information, you consent to the transfer of such information across country borders, and to the use, processing, and disclosure of such information in global locations. Your consent shall be deemed to include your consent to transfer of the personally identifiable or non-personally identifiable information to locations that may have different levels of privacy protection than in your own country.

### 12\. Links to Other Sites

This site provides links to other websites. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of all sites which you visit, including those whose links are provided so that you can understand how those sites collect, use and share your information. This site is not responsible for the privacy statements, content or data handling practices on other websites.

### 13\. Children's Privacy

This site does not knowingly intend to collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age.

If a child has provided us with personally identifiable information, a parent or guardian of that child may contact us at the email or mailing address listed in section 14 if they want this information deleted from our records. We will then make reasonable efforts to delete the child’s information from the database that stores information for this site.

### 14\. Contacting Us

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about this online privacy statement for this site, this site’s privacy practices, or have any questions regarding the contents of this website please contact us at

By Mail:

    BattleMetrics, LLC
    P.O. Box 980789
    Ypsilanti, MI 48198

OR By Email: [staff@battlemetrics.com](mailto:staff@battlemetrics.com)

We are committed to working with consumers to obtain a fair and rapid resolution of any complaints or disputes about privacy and the handling of your data. We will be happy to respond to your questions and comments.

### 15\. Privacy Statement Effective Date and Revision Days

Occasionally we may update the privacy statement for this site in order to reflect any changes to the website or our privacy practices. If we make any updates to this statement, including any updates reflecting material changes to our Online Behavioral/Interest-Based Advertising practices, the new statement will be posted to the website prior to the changes taking effect.

The effective date of this privacy statement is May 29, 2018.
